

Alfanisa Safvira

E.27/6, Bhayangkara Street, Benda Baru, Pamulang, South Tangerang. 15418.

+62 81510890339 alfanisasafvira@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/alfanisasafvira

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a student of Informatics Engineering at Syarif Hidayatullah State Islamic University Jakarta. In addition, I am a Bangkit Academy 2023 Cloud Computing Student Graduate. Also experienced in Student Organization as Secretary of Professional Department. Able to operate computers, write articles, time management, and learn easily.

OTHER SKILLS

- Algorithms and Programming
- Team work and Communicative
- Able to use Microsoft Office

WORK EXPERIENCE

Astra Financial

IT Infrastructure & Operations Intern December 2023 - March 2024

Astra Financial IT Helpdesk Intern September 2023 - December 2023

PT. Digikidz Indonesia

Computers and Robotics Instructors October 2019 - January 2020

FORMAL EDUCATION

Syarif Hidayatullah State Islamic University Jakarta

Faculty of Science and Technology Informatics Engineering 2020 - 2024

Vocational High School of Letris Indonesia 2 Software Engineering 2017 - 2020

ORGANISATIONAL / MANAGERIAL SKILLS

Informatics Engineering Student Association

Syarif Hidayatullah State Islamic University Jakarta Secretary of the Professional Department June 2022 - June 2023

Facilitating the development of skills and competencies of Informatics Engineering students in the field of Information Technology.

Student Cooperation

Syarif Hidayatullah State Islamic University Jakarta PR Staff and Members

June 2021 - Present

Create content for official social media. Devise strategies to support any new promotions or movements through the organization's editorial content.

CERTIFICATIONS

Artificial Intelligence

Certiport 2023

The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

Coursera

2023

System Administration and IT Infrastructure Service

Coursera

2023

Google Cloud Computing Foundations

Google Clouds Skills Boost 2023

Cybersecurity Essentials

Cisco Netwoking Academy 2022

Data Development Fundamental Linux

PASAS INSTITUTE

2022